

System Engineer seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Coding, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Application Support, MS SQL Server, Oracle, Java, Python, Excel, Unix Scripting, Data Structures, OOP, Shell Scripting



Current Designation: Systems Engineer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

Current Company: Infosys Limited Notice Period: 2 Months

Current Location: Pune Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Mechanical]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: System Engineer, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Coding, Web

Development, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Application Support, MS SQL Server, Oracle, Java, Python, Excel, Unix Scripting, Data Structures, OOP, Data Mining

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Skilled professional with 2 years of experience in Software Development, Application Programming, Coding, Web Development, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Application Support, MS SQL Server, Oracle, Java, Python, Excel, Unix Scripting, Data Structures, OOP, Data Mining

Work Experience

Infosys Limited as Systems Engineer

Nov 2018 to Till Date

Infosys Limited as Systems Engineer

Nov 2018 to Nov 2018

Systems Engineer Trainee

Infosys Limited

11/2018 - 04/2019, Mysore, India

Worked on MS SQL Server 2012-Essentials, Backup and

recovery, Monitoring.

Hands on experience on command line of Oracle 12c Database: Administration, essentials, Backup and Recovery / Worked on different levels of incidents.

Responsibilities: Close incident within SLA, Create scripts

for Hot or Cold backup of database.

Systems Engineer

Infosys Limited

05/2019 - 07/2019, Pune, India

Worked on POC of a Data Analytics project. Technology Used: Python, Tableau, Excel.

Responsibilities: Data Mining / Data Cleaning / Time

Forecasting / Report Generation.

Systems Engineer Infosys Limited

08/2019 - Present, Pune, India

Currently working in Automation team for Singapore

based client.

Technology Used: Python Scripting, Java, VBA, Shell

Scripting.

Responsibilities: Development of application as per client requirement / Automate the task which is used in client's regular job / Test application performance for potential bottlenecks and identify possible solutions

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Mechanical) from Maharishi Dayanand University (MDU), Rohtak in 2018

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Python	
MS SQL SERVER	
Big Data	
Unix scripting	
PowerShell Scripting	
oracle12c	
SQL	
OOP	
Data Structures	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
German				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time